Tell me how you think I'm wrong
When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love
You erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me
Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know
When I give away my trust
mammy or something trying to make this slideshow for you. I was trying to do this as best as I could.
Okay, sorry if it's not perfect. Sorry to do this as best as I could.
Aries, you're called the reckless pumpkin this year. Aries,
you reckless pumpkin you. And so Aries you've challenged death to a rematch three times this month.
your costume, the consequent.
So Aries stops speed running life like it's a side quest.
The prophecy for Aries,
the universe gives you one more warning
for it throws the whole cauldron.
Here's spooky symbol Aries,
a jack-o'-lantern with devil horns.
Okay, did everyone like that?
I mean, I'm trying to be the best I can.
Okay, the way I got Taurus, okay?
Are we ready for Taurus?
Don't know if you guys are ready or not you guys don't want this you guys you guys saying no you don't want you don't want to hear great horoscopes
No, you don't
Yes, I heard you. I thought I do I do
Okay
Already more okay
Where we got next areas we got tourists right?
Taurus the haunted buffet loves your is your religion and mashed potatoes are your sacrament
Taurus you'll leave the apocalypse if it has snacks or you survived the apocalypse, right?
Proposy for Taurus it goes complements your outfit take your deal
You'll finally get that raise
a spooky symbol
Vampires Chalice filled with merlot and regret
I hope you like that. Okay
I mean, am I doing okay? I mean, I'm trying to make it funny for everyone. Okay. Are you ready for the Gemini, the twin spark? Okay
No, nobody wants to hear. Nobody's I got I don't know what I'm doing. I don't know what I'm doing
I just don't know
Maybe I'm doing something good. Maybe it's I'm just an idiot. Okay. Gemini, you're the doppelganger
You'll meet your evil twin this Halloween. They're funnier than you
Try not to argue with your own reflection of parties, so the Gemini prophecy for Gemini attacks me for someone else, blows your cover, and serves a romance.
Spooky symbol for Gemini, two cracked masks whispering secrets.
There's nobody in the chat right now, like obviously nobody likes me on the show anymore.
I said shirtless, everyone, no one is here.
No, I'm not one person is in the chat. There is a one person then I might say, oh, okay
Not one person not one
Solitary soul. Let's hear the readings. Okay
So guys that's gonna be it for me
Since I got not one person to say something nice not one person to like you know say hey
I support you not one person not there's zero people literally zero people in the chat
Um, I quit YouTube officially and I will see you never again. Bye
You and ghost with your halo
Airplane mode I felt it in my skin. So I was seen like design
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we've learned
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you craved the chaos I fed, cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna crush you
I could never rise above
this resurrection don't call it rage it's recollection not to be divine but i love you
this sin was born from your reflection
we trade halos for horns it's fair every wound you gave i wear
we take turns being the villains muse but damn it i still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from the stranger's lair
Just to prove that I still care, you'd fall apart
Cause you know it's true, no one sins the way I do
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna, cause you, I could never